人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：Iz    红豆包    奈奈良
校对：Iz          总监   IZ
时间轴：今        后期：吉吉
《开心汉堡店》
第三季第十八集
出发去佛罗里达
Going to Florida.
阳光明媚的佛罗里达
Sunshiney, Florida.
现在就启程
Now-ow.
出发去佛罗里达
Going to Florida.
佛罗里达  佛罗里达
Florida, Florida.
人人都向往
Everyone's going somehow.
唱得不错  老妈
Great song, Mom.
别发牢骚了
Hey, sourpuss.
你想怎样  留下来工作么
What are you gonna do, stay here and work?
餐馆正消毒呢
The restaurant's being fumigated.
刚好可以趁此机会去南部看我爸妈的新家
It's the perfect time to go down and see my parent's new condo.
我宁愿消毒器喷我嘴里毒死我
Ugh, I'd rather let a fumigator spray poison in my mouth
也不想和你父母住一起
than stay with your parents.
-鲍鲍  别这样  -好吧他们很好
- Bobby, stop it. - No, they're nice.
佛罗里达是我国长得最像小鸡鸡的州了
Florida's our most penis-shaped state.
-哪个地理老师教你们的  -叮咚老师
- Who's your geography teacher? - Mr. Ding-Dong.
我满脑子只想着那个游泳池  太酷了
I'm just thinking about that pool. Oh, man.
游泳池  游泳池  游泳池
Pool, pool, pool.
我要坐那个滑梯
I'm gonna go down the slide. Whoo.
我倒滑过  不  我没有
I went down backwards. No, I didn't.
你们开心就好
Well, I'm glad you kids are excited,
我反正是打算自尽了
because I am going to kill myself.
-鲍勃  -太好了
- Bob. - Yes!
够了  我父母看到小外孙和外孙女们
Enough. My parents are gonna be so excited
一定会非常高兴的
to see their little grandbabies.
我们见到他们也会很开心
And we are gonna be excited to see them.
出发去佛罗里达  温暖的佛罗里达
Going to Florida, tropical Florida
-吉恩  -佛罗里达海牛
- Hey! Gene!  - Manatees Florida, now.
海牛  大型水栖食草性哺乳动物  需在温暖的水域中生存
你们真的没必要大老远跑过来
You really didn't have to come all this way.
-当然有必要了  -既然来都来了
- Of course we did. - Well, it's done.
也没必要讨论这个了
So, you know, you're here, so...
你们在这里过得好吗  艾尔
So, uh, how are you enjoying the place, Al?
我们还在适应中
Oh, we're still adjusting.
那边一身豹纹紧身衣的是什么  花豹吗
What am I looking at over there in leopard-print tights? A leopard?
我跟他们说过很多次了
I've told them a hundred times.
那是海伦・凯勒曼  她有些神经质
Oh, that's Helen Kellerman. She's nuts.
故事很棒  姥姥  你还是那么会讲
Okay, great story, Grandma. Uh, you still got it.
爱你们  想你们  游泳池在哪儿
Love you, miss you, and where's the pool?
耳部感染  我们来了
Ear infection, here we come.
好吧  玩得开心
Okay, go have fun.
抱歉  格罗瑞娅
Sorry, Gloria.
看来你对噪音还是很敏感
I guess you've still got that thing about loud noises.
有什么计划吗  我们该做什么
So, what's the plan? What should we do?
今晚我和艾尔打算去参加
Well, tonight, Al and I are supposed
百乐餐  每人自带一道菜的聚会
-一个百乐餐  但是  -我们也去吧
- to go to a potluck, but, uh... - Hey, we could all go.
不行  我是说  你们不会想去的
No! I mean, you don't want to go to that.
百乐餐有什么意思  这里好玩的多着呢
Potluck? There's so many other fun things to do around here:
麻将
Mahjongg.
对哦  -不
Yeah. - No.
跳棋
Chinese checkers.
-不  -对对
- No. - Yeah, yeah.
-室外地滚球  -室外地滚球  -不
- Boccie. - Oh, boccie. - No.
-双陆棋  -不
- Backgammon. - No.
-麻将  -你说过了
- Mahjongg. - Oh. You said that.
我不记得我说过麻将
I don't remember saying mahjongg.
你说过了  你一开始就说了
You did, you said it first.
品酒会
Wine tasting.
-很好  就是它了  -好哇  品酒
- That. Let's do that. As... - Ooh, yay, wine.
我们尽快  好吗
As soon as we can, right?
我们能现在就去品酒吗
Can we go taste wine now?
我还没在奥运会规格的游泳池里撒过尿呢
Uh, I've never peed in an Olympic-size pool.
不知道能不能拿金牌  好紧张
I'm a little nervous about going for the gold.
放轻松  吉恩
Relax, Gene.
今天你多年的苦练终于要有结果了
This is where all those years of training pay off.
"关门清洗"
"Closed for cleaning"?
不
No!
好  好  好  冷静  冷静
Okay, okay, okay, calm down, calm down.
我们可以自己灌水  那儿有个饮水喷头
We can fill it. There's a drinking fountain.
我们  我们需要一个水桶
Okay, we just... we need a bucket.
水桶在哪儿
Where are the buckets?
别管水桶了  吐口水吧
Forget the bucket, just spit.
我嘴是干的  蒂娜  给我吐点你的
My mouth's dry. Tina, give me some of your spit.
-没对准  再来  -不不不不
- You missed. Try again. - Oh, no! No, no, no!
不  不  我们的旅行全毁了
Oh, no, no! Our trip is ruined.
我用掉了所有的假期只为这一刻
I used all my vacation days for this!
现在怎么办  我可不要坐着看夕阳
Now what? I'm not gonna sit and watch the sunset
还有这帮不知道在搞什么的家伙
or whatever these people do.
要我说我们去古巴吧  泳具我们都有了
I say we go to Cuba. We've got the floaties.
我一直想去看看猪猡湾  听着很可爱
I've always wanted to see the Bay Of Pigs. Sounds cute.
猪猡湾  位于巴西西南海岸
看  是那个神经质的花豹夫人
Hey, look, it's the crazy leopard lady.
我的贝琦
My Bitsy...
曲子真销魂
Wow, that's bewitching.
是吹给我死去的狗狗贝琦听的
It's for my dead dog, Bitsy.
它生前很喜欢这首曲子
He used to love the sound of this thing.
-听你吹之前我也挺喜欢  -它咋死的
- I used to love it, too. - How'd Bitsy die?
-巨蟒吃了它  -佛罗里达有巨蟒吗
- Python ate him. - There's pythons in Florida?
旅游指南里可没写这个
They didn't mention that in the brochure.
我们这里无奇不有
Oh, we got everything here.
蟒蛇  黑豹  食肉的臭虫
Pythons, panthers, predatory stink bugs.
是的  真是应有尽有
Yup, that's everything.
你怎么知道你的狗是被巨蟒吃了
How do you know your dog got eaten by a python?
-它留了字条吗  -两周前
- Did it leave a note? - Two weeks ago,
我看见我的小贝琦进了这片树林
I saw my little Bitsy go into these woods.
接着我在里面看到了巨蟒
Then I saw the python in there.
你们自己推理吧
You do the math.
不  谢了  我们是来度假的
Ah, no thanks. We're on vacation.
你推吧  你自己推吧
You do the math. You do it.
老年品酒会
红酒和白酒真是相得益彰啊
Wow, the red pairs nicely with the white.
看看这些活跃的老人们
Look at all these active seniors.
我都想赶紧变老  自己也搬到这边来了
I can't wait to get old and move down here myself.
琳  我得告诉你一件事
Lin, there's something you should know.
-听了别伤心  -怎么了  什么事
- Now don't get upset. - What? What happened?
这个地方
Uh, this place
有点特殊
is kind of special.
-我看得出来  -这里的老人都很活跃
- I can see that. - The seniors are active.
-非常活跃  -是的  我已经说过了
- Very active. - Yeah, I said that already.
我的意思是  他们很开放
I mean, like adventurous.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
Okay.
我喂你
I got one.
如果不乱搞  生活还有什么意义
天哪  琳
Oh, my God, Lin.
他们搞的是交换性伴侣派对
These people are swingers.
什么  你是说像跳舞那样摇摆吗
What, like-like dancers?
一词多义  "swing"有"交换性伴侣"和"摇摆"的意思
-不  -不
- No. - No.
像打高尔夫那样
Like golfers?
不是
No.
是的
Yeah.
啥  啥  啥  交换...
Wha, wha, wha, wha, swi...
什么
What? Huh? Oh.
我为贝琦感到遗憾  这是它吗
I'm sorry about Bitsy. Is this him?
它穿的可真时髦
He was a snazzy dresser.
-等等  那条蛇多大  -至少十英尺
- Wait, how big was this snake? - At least ten feet.
十英尺的蛇  在这里面吗
Ten feet of snake? In there?
他会紧紧的勒住你
Oh, he'd put the squeeze on you.
我跟社区物管反映  要他们除掉它
I told the condo association get rid of it.
他们却不相信我
They don't believe me.
但那条蛇就在里面  会吃人
But that snake's in there, and it's a killer,
我会证明这一点的
and I'm gonna prove it.
所以我才带了摄像机
That's why I got this.
唯一的问题是  我腿脚不太方便
The only problem is, I don't walk so well.
你们可以进去啊
You kids could go in there.
-我会付你们钱  -什么  不行
- I'll pay ya. - What?! No!
吉恩  让海伦说完
Gene, let Helen speak.
一百美金怎么样
Well, what would you say to a $100?
-天哪  -不行
- Oh, my God! - No.
-可以  -可以
- Yes. - Yes!
但是你们得拍到蛇  没证据  就没钱
But you've got to get it on there. No proof, no money.
-不行  -为了一百美金
- No. - For a hundred bucks,
-我们一定会拍到那条蛇  -不行
- we will get that thing on tape. - No.
-不管是搞外遇  -不行
- Cheating on his wife. - No.
-受贿  -不行
- Taking bribes. - No.
-在蛇用品店偷窃  -不行
- Uh, shoplifting from a snake mall. - No.
-还是放弃他的梦想  -不行
- Uh, giving up on his dreams. - No.
我们什么都拍得到
We're going to get it all!
自从在佛罗里达放生了第一条缅甸蟒蛇
Since the first Burmese pythons were released in Florida,
这些贪婪的食肉动物
these voracious predators have spread
就从佛罗里达西北部蔓延到了大沼泽地
from the panhandle to the Everglades.
-海伦并没有疯  -起码在这点上没有
- So Helen's not crazy. - At least not about this.
它们吃兔子  浣熊  小狗
They eat rabbits, raccoons, small dogs,
甚至连鹿都吃
even deer.
我还太小  不想变成蛇的腹中之物
I'm too young to be an outline in a snake's belly!
吉恩  冷静点
Gene, get a grip!
我们说的可是一百美金
We're talking about a hundred dollars.
你有次为了咬一口燕麦卷还舔过鼻涕虫呢
You once licked a slug for a bite of a granola bar.
鼻涕虫和燕麦卷很配好不好
Slugs go well with granola!
别担心  吉恩  只要我们团结一致
Don't worry, Gene. As long as we stick together,
蛇是不可能把我们都吞进去的
the snake can't swallow all of us.
说到团结一致  我看我就不跟着去了吧
Speaking of sticking together, how about I don't go with you?
我会呆在大本营
I'll stay at base camp.
我来当  操作电脑的
I'll be the guy who's, uh... good with computers.
请叫我  "后方观察员"
Call me... Circuit Breaker.
我才不要叫你那个
I'm not calling you that.
我觉得你真该那么叫  因为
I really think you should, because, um,
我正在潜入主机
I'm hacking into the mainframe.
数据加密
Oh, oh, encryption.
搞定啦
Ha, ha. Right around ya.
启动拼写检查
And, oh... Activate spellcheck.
走你  我进去了
Go. I'm in!
那两个人也是么
What about those two?
是的
Yes.
那个大耳垂和秃顶老头呢
How about, uh, Earlobes and uh, Back Hair?
别告诉我他们也玩那个
Don't tell me they're into it.
你不会想知道他们有多爱玩那个
You don't want to know how into it they are.
真是难以置信
That is unbelievable.
这不好笑  鲍勃  太恶心了
Oh, it's not funny, Bob. It's gross.
不  琳  这真是太有意思了
No, Lin, it's really funny.
妈  这是
Ma, this is wh...
你为什么想这么做
Why would you want to do that?
你们为什么想住在这里
Why would you want to live here?
因为其它地方都太可怕
Because the other places were horrible!
老人都在等死
Old people waiting to die.
而只有在这儿  大家才有朝气
This place, the people are alive.
相当有朝气
They're really alive.
-太棒了  -闭嘴
- That's amazing. - Stop it!
我们想着  如果那是他们生活的一部分
We thought, if swinging is part of it,
我们为什么不尝试一下呢
why not give it a try?
于是我们搬来这  你父亲却临阵退缩了
Then we moved here, and your father got cold feet.
好样的  老爸
Good for your feet, Dad.
才不好  一点都不好  艾尔
It's not good! It's not good, Al!
不好
No!
海伦  能给我块全麦饼干吗
Can I have a graham cracker, Helen?
自己买去
Get your own.
我们可以去当
You know, we could become
职业的巨蟒赏金猎人
professional python bounty hunters.
可以搬来这拍我们自己的真人秀
We could move here and start our own reality TV show.
节目就叫  《蟒行无限》
We could call it Snake It to the Limit.
"Take It to the Limit" 歌名  收录于老鹰乐队第四张专辑
或者叫《蟒林争霸》
Or So You Think You Can Snake.
"So You Think You Can Dance" 《舞林争霸》美国一档舞蹈真人秀节目
或者叫  《蟒味佳肴》
Or Snake and Bake,
"Shake and Bake" 一种以面包屑  猪肉  鸡肉为原料的创意菜品
我们逮住它后可以把它做成一道菜
if we baked the snake after we caught it.
喂  我付钱是让你们抓蛇  不是唠嗑
Hey, I'm paying you kids to track, not yak.
别这么猴急嘛 海伦
Hey, don't get your tights in a bunch, Helen.
我们这就动身找巨蟒去了
We're gonna find that snake.
回见  吉恩
See ya, Gene.
我能吃块甜瓜吗
Can I have some melon?
不行
No.
这边一定有好多
There must be millions of places in here
可以让巨蟒藏身的地方
where that snake could hide.
好吧  也许没那么多
Okay, maybe not millions.
我们再走一遍看看
Let's try that again.
佛罗里达真奇怪
Florida's weird.
怎么回事  你们不是才走吗
What's going on? You just left.
海伦  别影响我们工作
Ugh. Let us work, Helen!
那就赶紧工作呀
Then work!
没看见我们正在做吗  我的天
We're working! God!
没打中
Ha! You missed!
对啊  你没打中
Yeah, you missed.
等下
Wait.
我不想那群淫荡的
I don't want all these old
老毒物靠近我爸妈
horny toads anywhere near my parents.
他们怎么就掺和进这种事了
I can't believe they got mixed up in all this.
放松点  琳  你爸妈都是成年人了
Easy, Lin. Your parents are adults.
这事儿我们其实管不着
It's really none of our business.
回去后有猛料爆了
I'm telling everybody when we get home.
天  我脑子里都是那些画面
Ugh! I can't get the image out of my mind.
一群裸体的老头老太太
A bunch of naked old people
全都在...  裸着
all in a... yuck, naked.
孩子们
Oh, hi, kids!
-都在干嘛  -快看那儿
- All in a what? - Uh... look, over there!
-咋了  -骗到你们了
- What? - I got you.
睡觉吧
Go to bed.
都去睡觉  现在马上
All of you. Bed now.
其实我们打算今晚去
Actually, we were thinking we'd camp out tonight
树林旁的停车场露营
in the parking lot by the woods.
艾尔姥爷说我们可以用他的帐篷
Grandpa Al said we could use his tent. Huh?
在停车场吗
In the parking lot?
可以避开这里吗
Away from this?
那太好了  太好了
That's great! Yeah, great!
要是有人请你们参加百乐餐  千万别去
But if anyone invites you to a potluck, run away.
要办百乐餐吗
There's a potluck?!
不是你喜欢的那种
You would not like it.
真的吗  你说的是哪种
Really? What do you mean?
一言难尽
It's hard to explain why you wouldn't like it.
你就说说看嘛
Well, give me some ideas.
我喜欢大家自带菜品的感觉
I love the idea of everyone bringing a dish.
我的天
Oh, God!
别当我们面就搞起来  拜托
Don't do it while we're here, please!
琳达  我们收到了
Linda, we've been served
未履约通知
with a Notice of Failure to Perform.
啥  未履约  怎么回事
What? Failure? W-Why? Wha...?
你父母拒绝了我们的百乐餐邀请
Your parents RSVP'd "No" to the potluck.
很明显他们无意
It's clear they have no intention
全身心投入我们的活动
of taking part fully in the activities here.
不参加活动的人就不能住这了
And those who don't play can't stay.
不能住这了
They can't?
今晚的百乐餐是他们最后一次机会
Tonight's potluck was their third strike.
他们已经错过了"最佳球"高尔夫远足
They also missed the Best Ball golf outing
和"国境之南"墨西哥鱼肉卷之夜
and the South of the Border fish taco night.
等等  你们就因为这个要赶走他们吗
Wait. So you're kicking them out for not going to your parties?
你们有什么权利这么做
You can do that?
这是我们字体放大版合约里的规定之一
It's in our bylaws, large print edition.
要成为社区的一份子就得遵守
You've got to be part of the community.
我爸妈可不要跟你们同流合污
Well, these pots are keeping their lids on!
别来烦他们
Stay away from their beef and noodles!
我要去睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
我希望你们找蛇的技术
I hope you're better at finding snakes
比搭帐篷强点
than pitching tents,
因为帐篷搭得真是烂透了
because you stink.
我倒希望你赶紧找到钱包
Well, I hope you're good at finding your purse
准备好付那一百块钱
and ponying up that hundred bucks.
-我有的是钱  -是吗
- I got the money. - Yeah?
-是的  -是吗
- Yeah. - Yeah?
-是啊  -是吗
- Yeah! - Yeah?!
那让我看看啊
Let me see it!
用不着你担心  我给得起
Hey, don't you worry. I'm good for it.
那你倒是给我十块啊
Just put ten dollars in my hand.
-晚安  -晚安  海伦
- Good night. - Good night, Helen.
做个好梦啊
Sweet dreams, okay?
我爱你  海伦
I love you, Helen!
更爱你的钱
And I love your money!
天黑了
Uh, it's getting dark.
我该到帐篷里去看守我们的大本营了
I better go in the tent and do base camp stuff.
天哪  帐篷长腿跑了
Oh, no! The tent's running away.
快回来好好在营地呆着  吉恩
Oh, get back here with base camp, Gene!
我不要
I don't want to!
海伦说要给你饼干
Helen said she'll get you crackers!
放屁  我没说过
No, I didn't!
睡你的觉去吧
Oh, go to bed, already!
别担心  妈
Don't you worry, Mom.
我确定你和我爸
I'm sure you and Dad can find
能找到一个更好的退休社区
a nice retirement community.
在那儿你能坐着打秋千
One where a porch swing is something you sit on
"swing"  还有"秋千"的意思
而不是被迫乱搞
and not strap into.
我坐过那个  怪怪的
I sat on that. It was weird.
我们没钱去住退休社区了
We won't be able to afford to live in a retirement community.
公寓我们都租不起
Or even an apartment.
-什么  为什么  -为什么
- What? Why? - Why?
如果被赶走  我们的定金也拿不回来了
If we get kicked out, we'll have to forfeit our down payment.
不是吧
No.
你知道我怎么想吗
Well, you know what I'm thinking.
-不  不要  -你们可以...
- No, no. - You could always...
-不不不  不行  -搬来
- No, no, no. No. - ...move in...
-不行不行  -和我们一起住
- No, no. - ...with us.
不
No!
那是什么动物的叫声
What kind of animal was that?
别吓的跟小鸡崽子似的  成吗
Stop being scared, okay?
你要吓着蒂娜了
You're gonna spook Tina.
我不是被吓着了  而是被吓到快吐了
I'm not spooked. What's the thing after spooked? I'm that.
等等  我们都呆在帐篷里吧
Wait, wait! Let's all stay in the tent.
可以叫帐篷服务啊
Let's order tent service!
我要...  好难选
I'll get... Ooh. Ooh, this is hard.
我要科布沙拉和...
I'll get the Cobb salad and...
你俩要什么  我帮你们点个
What do you guys want? Okay, I'll just put you down
烤鸡翅和莳萝三文鱼吧
for some spicy wings and, like, a dill salmon.
还要别的吗
What else?
姐妹们  姐妹们
Guys! Guys!
是你的"嘘"声还是蟒蛇的"嘶"声
Did you say "Shh"? Or did the snake say "Sss"?
那是什么
What was that?
别拿手电筒照我眼睛
Qu-quit shining the light in my eyes!
我觉得我身上有什么东西
I think something's on me.
-有东西没  -有
- Is there something on me? - Uh, yes.
可能是羽毛  也可能是蝎子
It's either a feather or a scorpion.
把它拿走
Get it off!
蒂娜  停下  停下  我就拿走
Tina, stop! Stop! I'll get it!
不不不  现在我看不见蝎子了
No, no, no, no, no! Now I can't see the scorpion!
就地打滚
Drop and roll!
也许就是根羽毛
Maybe it was a feather.
你就想是羽毛吧
Just think feather.
我讨厌羽毛
I hate feathers.
我的天
Oh, God. Oh.
-别叽歪了  -不要
- Oh, stop it. - Oh, no.
既然他们没地方住  就该和我们住
If they need a place to live they will live with us, Bob!
这事就这么定了  鲍勃
Case closed!
就不能让他们跟你妹住吗
Well, why can't they live with your sister?
反正她已经是一团糟了
Her life is already ruined.
盖尔住的是一居室
Gayle has a studio apartment.
我们有仨孩子却只有一个浴室
We have three kids and one bathroom.
别废话了  鲍勃
Not another word, Bob.
如果他们被赶走  就跟我们一起住
If they get kicked out of here, then they are staying with us.
那好  他们绝对不会被赶走的
Well, then they are not going to get kicked out of here.
-啥  -先走了
- What? - Excuse me.
-鲍勃  你去哪儿  -不去哪儿
- Bob, where are you going? - Nowhere.
-你要干嘛  -不干嘛
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
-鲍勃  -拜
- Bob. - Bye.
蟒蛇猎人呼唤蟒蛇懦夫  完毕
Snake-hunter to Snake-wuss. Over.
蟒蛇懦夫收...  说什么呢
Snake-wuss to... Hey.
我们迷路了  手电筒也掉了
We're lost, our flashlights are gone
我们也找不到出树林的路
and we can't find our way out of the woods,
这里可能到处是蝎子  或羽毛  完毕
which is possibly full of scorpions... or feathers. Over.
跟着我的声音走
Follow the sound of my voice!
我们用的是对讲机  吉恩
It's on the walkie-talkie, Gene.
那就跟着你的心
Then follow your heart.
不会错的
You can't go wrong!
闭嘴  闭嘴吧
Shush! Just shush!
蒂娜  我们自救吧
Tina, let's think.
有夜间蝴蝶这种东西吗
Is there such a thing as night butterflies?
拜托说有
Please say yes.
还是有可能是蝴蝶的
It could still be butterflies.
好吧  不是
No, they're not.
你好  艾尔
Hi, Al.
派对看起来很有意思啊
Looks like a pretty fun party.
你们只需去亮个相就行了  不是吗
I mean, look, all you got to do is show up, right?
这样他们就会让你们留下来了
And then they'll let you stay.
亮相后也得参与其中啊
Show up and... and play.
是啊  你们不正是为此而来的吗
Well, yeah, but, you know, that's why you came here, right?
肯定也是向往这种生活才来的嘛
I mean, you must have been excited about it at some point.
发生什么事了
What-what happened?
我看过其他老头子
I saw all these other fellas.
-他们就是一群臭屁鬼  -明白
- They're just a bunch of... peacocks. - Mmm. Oh.
你也不想被大家遗忘在角落无人问津吧
Y-you don't want to be the last breadstick in the basket, huh?
有那种
There's, uh...
小药丸  你懂吧
breadstick pills, you know?
医生不让我吃
Doc won't let me take those pills.
说对心脏  肾脏
Bad heart... and kidney...
-肝脏不好  -好吧
- liver... - Right.
还会腿疼  口干
And leg pains and dry mouth.
好吧  那你平时都用什么
W-well, what else gets you going?
你有什么特殊的癖好吗  像是...
Is there anything you're into? Like, uh...
像是脚掌控之类的
I don't know... uh, feet or something?
皮鞭
Leather?
打屁股
Spanking?
我实在想不出其他的了
Um, I don't really know any others.
有一样东西
Well, there's one thing.
格罗瑞娅也不知道
Gloria doesn't know.
什么  是什么
What? What-what is it?
算  算了吧
Eh. F-forget it.
你可以跟我说的  艾尔
You can tell me, Al.
-气球  -啥
- Balloons. - What?
-气球  -很好
- Balloons! - Um, that's great.
我  等下  什么意思
I... Wait. What is that?
我喜欢  看女人吹气球
I like... to watch a woman inflate a balloon
然后坐爆它
and then sit on it till it pops.
那让我疯  疯狂
It drives me cra-crazy.
不  那  我是说  你喜欢这个啊
No, that's... I mean, that's what you're into.
对  但格罗瑞娅讨厌噪音  行不通的
Yeah, but Gloria hates loud noises. It'd never work.
-非得爆吗  -是的  要爆  要爆
- Uh, does it have to pop? - Yes! Pop! Pop! Yes!
你从哪儿看来的这个
What... Where'd-where'd you see that first?
因特网
World Wide Web.
我  我得  我得去找来看看
Uh, I've... I'll have to, um... I'll check it out.
-你就  就  输入"www  点
You just... You just, uh... www-dot...
女人吹气球再坐爆气球  点 com"
Women-inflates-a-balloon-and- sits-on-it-and-pops-it-dot-com.
网址很好记嘛
Yeah. Catchy name.
我们怎么还在这里面
How are we still in here?
这真是全世界最小的森林了
This is the tiniest forest in the world!
我怎么突然感觉变慢了
All of a sudden I feel slower.
-也变矮了  -我们走进沼泽了
- And shorter. - We're in a mud hole.
我受够了  我讨厌佛罗里达
That's it! I hate Florida!
吉恩  快来帮我们  我们陷沼泽里了
Gene, come help us! We're gonna drown in mud
-还可能有蛇来吃我们  -我不信
- if the snake doesn't eat us first. - I don't believe you.
给我发一张你们拿着今天的报纸的照片
Send me a picture of you in the mud holding today's newspaper.
在那之前  我会关掉对讲机
Until you do, I am turning off the walkie-talkie.
吉恩  别关  别关
Gene, don't do it! Don't do it!
他关了  你死定了  吉恩
He did it. You're dead to me, Gene!
我们也快死了  所以情况很复杂
And we'll be dead, too, so it's complicated.
-救命  -救命
- Help! - Help!
救命  救命
Help! Help!
*我不怕鬼*
*I'm not afraid of ghosts*
*我不怕鲨鱼*
*I'm not afraid of sharks*
*我不怕癌症*
*I'm not afraid of cancer*
*我就怕蛇*
*I'm just afraid of snakes*
*我怕得要死*
*They really creep me out*
*蛇没胳膊没腿*
*Where are their arms and legs?*
*让我受不了*
*It's not okay!*
我觉得吉恩不会来了
I don't think Gene's coming.
少想多喊
Less thinking, more screaming!
大声点
Louder!
大不了了  但我可以加上动作
I can't, but I'll add gestures.
我的天哪
Oh, God!
怪不得他们要清洗游泳池呢
No wonder they had to clean the pool.
下流的老鸭子们
Dirty old ducks.
下流鸭子
Dirty ducks
Dirty ducks.
下流鸭子
嘎  嘎
Quack, quack.
嗨  格罗瑞娅
Hi, Gloria.
抱歉  抱歉吓到你了
Oh, sorry. Sorry to startle you.
我知道你不喜欢噪音
I know that's your thing. Okay. So, uh...
-你在干嘛呢  洗碗吗  -是的
- so, what are you doing? Dishes? - Yeah. I guess
我想我该把这地方收拾收拾了
I'm gonna have to pack this place up.
也许不用
Well, actually, maybe not.
猜猜谁跟艾尔谈了性爱派对的事儿
Guess who's been talking to Al about sex parties?
-谁  -在下
- Who? - This guy.
再猜猜谁发现了连你都不知道的
And guess who found out Al's secret kink
艾尔的秘密癖好
that even you didn't know about?
-谁  -我  我发现了  本人
- Who? - Me. I did. Right here.
-是什么  -说出来可能会吓到你
- What is it? - Well, the answer may startle you. Literally.
你有耳塞或耳机吗
Do you have any earplugs or headphones?
-还有气球  -啥
- And balloons? - Huh?
还有自带的菜  因为是百乐餐嘛
And something to share, 'cause it's a potluck.
我们也得准备点什么  冰箱里有什么
So we should whip something up. What do you got in the fridge?
我快坚持不住了
Can't hold on much longer.
蒂娜  帮我录一下遗言
Tina, help me record my last will and testament.
你看到这个的时候  我已经死了
If you're watching this, I'm dead.
我只有几句话要说
And I only have a few things to say.
别碰我的东西
Don't touch my stuff!
谁都不能分
No one gets anything!
我把所有东西都留给我的鬼魂
I leave it all to my ghost!
那是啥玩意儿
What the hell is that?
吉恩  你来了
Gene, you came!
快  抓住这个
Quick. Grab this.
你救了我们  吉恩  我的命是你的了
You saved us, Gene. I owe you my life.
谢谢  不用了
No, thanks.
你的命我看过了  不怎么想要
I've seen it, and I'm not impressed.
黄肚皮[形容胆小鬼]  吉恩
Yellow Belly! Gene!
你肚皮也没我想的那么黄嘛
Your belly's not as yellow as I thought.
-你怎么想通了  -我不想变成独生子
- What happened? - I didn't want to be an only child.
独生子都是怪胎
They're always weird.
吉恩给我们开了条路  带我们出去吧
Gene mowed us a path. Drive us out of here.
我讨厌佛罗里达  我讨厌佛罗里达
I hate Florida. I hate Florida.
讨厌  讨厌  讨厌
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
-看哪  是贝琦的小短裙  -是的
- Look. Bitsy's tutu. - Ah. Yeesh.
想必那蛇平时都来这儿消化它的猎物
This must be the place the snake comes to digest its prey.
是贝琦
It's Bitsy!
他没被吸收  从蛇体内被排除来了
He passed right through the snake without being digested!
就像我那次吞下一颗纽扣一样
Like that time I swallowed a button!
就是这颗
This button.
我父母呢
Where are my parents?
为派对做准备去了
Um, getting ready for the party.
-啥  -咋了
- What?! - Wha...?
这是怎么回事
What is going on?
你说啥
What?!
去吧  你们俩  玩开心点儿
Go! Go, you two. Have fun.
-好吧  -啥
- Okay. - What?!
拜拜
Okay, bye!
我们走了
We're going now!
-拜拜  -谢谢你  鲍勃
- Bye-bye. - Thank you, Bob.
不客气  艾尔
No problem, Al.
我没跟你说话
Oh, no. I wasn't talking to you.
鲍勃  我要你现在告诉我这是怎么回事
Bob, you tell me what is happening right now.
艾尔终于找到秘诀了
Al finally got into the swing of things.
他们去参加派对了  也就是说
They're going to the party, which means
他们不会被赶走了  也就是说我是英雄
they won't be kicked out, which means I'm a hero.
你把我父母搞去参加性爱派对
Oh, you're a hero 'cause you got my parents
就成英雄了
to go to a sex party?!
好吧  英雄可能太夸张了  但
Well, maybe not a hero, but, uh, eh.
太好了  这样他们就能留下来
Great, so they get to stay here
像饭前点心一样被换来换去
and get passed around like hors d'oeuvres?!
裤裆还夹着螃蟹
With crabs! In their crotches!
琳达  看看他们
Linda, look at them.
天哪  他们有20年
Oh, my God. They haven't kissed each other
-没接过吻了  -看出来了
- in 20 years. - Ooh, it shows.
我相信他们的接吻技术会越来越好的
I'm sure they'll get better at it.
看来爱他就得让他去乱搞了
Huh. I guess if you love something, you let it go swing.
-气球是干嘛用的  -一言难尽
- What's with the balloons? - Oh, it's a long story.
我有点想试试这个
Actually, I kind of want to try something.
你对这有感觉吗
Does this do anything for you?
有一点
Maybe...
我看蟒蛇只存在于海伦的想象中吧
Well, I guess the only python was in Helen's head.
《脑中蛇灾》  有没有
"Snakes on a brain." Am I right?
《空中蛇灾》  2006年美国惊悚电影
-说得好  -我都等不及想看
- Yes, you are correct! - I can hardly wait
海伦见到贝琦之后的表情了
to see the look on Helen's face when we reunite her with Bitsy.
又是你们  怎么了
Oh, you again. What do you got?
把钱准备好吧  海伦  最好是去银行
Get your purse out, Helen. Better yet, go to the bank
把保险箱取出来  我们有好消息了
and open up your safe... we've got good news.
你们抓到蛇了吗
You got the snake?
比那更好
Better.
贝琦
Bitsy!
你的衣服怎么不见了
Oh, what happened to your clothes?
咱们换睡裤吧
Let's get you into your big-dog pants.
快回来
Come back!
-贝琦  -也许它不想穿衣服
- Bitsy! - Maybe he doesn't like wearing clothes.
要是有那样的身材  我也不会想穿的
With that body, I wouldn't either.
-贝琦  -我去
- Bitsy! - Oh, man.
这样我们永远别想拿到那100块钱了
We're never gonna get our hundred bucks now.
贝琦
Bitsy!
贝琦在里面过得貌似挺开心的
Bitsy seemed really happy in there,
-这能让你好受点吗  -是吗
- if it makes you feel any better. - Oh, yeah?
贝琦
Uh, Bitsy!
不管你想做什么  我都支持你
Whatever you want to do, I support you!
贝琦  听  是你最喜欢的
Bitsy, listen! Your favorite!
我的贝琦小宝贝
My little Bitsy baby
贝琦  贝琦
Bitsy. Bitsy
贝琦  我的贝琦  宝贝儿
Bitsy. Oh, my Bitsy, baby
贝琦  我会想你的  我的贝琦
Bitsy, I'm gonna miss ya, my Bitsy. Bitsy!
-再见  -再见  也可能永远不见了
- Bye! - Bye! Good-bye forever maybe!
再见  妈妈  再见  爸爸
Bye, Ma! Bye, Dad!
我们永远不会忘记这次度假的
We'll never forget it.
我们能在他们不清洗泳池的时候再回来吗
Can we come back sometime when they're not cleaning the pool?
-不行  -绝对不行  想都别想
- No. Never. - Absolutely not. Not a chance in hell.
今天早上和姥姥姥爷
Who were those people eating breakfast
-一起吃早餐的人是谁啊  -是啊
- with Gram and Gramps this morning? - Yeah.
是麦迪逊夫妇
Oh, those were the Madisons.
为什么麦迪逊先生要坐在姥姥的大腿上
Well, why was Mr. Madison sitting on Gram-Gram's lap?
她从来不让我们坐  我可是要求过
She never lets us sit there. And I have asked.
亲爱的  他老了  以为姥姥是椅子呢
Honey, he's old. He-he thought she was a chair.
没错  没错
Right, right.
你们几个应该没看到昨晚的派对吧
Um, you kids didn't see any of the party last night, did you?
没有  但我们能听见
No, but we could hear it.
那些人得改改习惯
Those people should learn
别在百乐餐聚会上扎气球
to have a potluck without popping all those balloons.
滚床单也别太大声
And without having really loud sex.
*我不怕鬼*
*I'm not afraid of ghosts*
*我不怕鲨鱼*
*I'm not afraid of sharks*
*我不怕癌症*
*I'm not afraid of cancer*
*我就怕蛇*
*I'm just afraid of snakes*
*我怕得要死*
*They really creep me out*
*蛇没胳膊没腿*
*Where are their arms and legs?*
*让我受不了*
*It's not okay!*
*我不怕鬼*
I'm not afraid of ghosts
*我不怕鲨鱼*
I'm not afraid of sharks
*我不怕癌症*
I'm not afraid of cancer
*我就怕蛇*
I'm just afraid of snakes
*我怕得要死*
They really creep me out
*蛇没胳膊没腿*
Where are their arms and legs?
*让我受不了*
*It's not okay!*
我的贝琦  宝贝  贝琦*
*Oh, my Bitsy, baby, Bitsy*
*我会想你的
*I'm gonna miss ya.*